

# Personal Information

**23.05.1999** 

+994 55 623 05 99

narimanli.murad@gmail.com

Baku, Sabail district, Badamdar settle ment, Ganjlar street

in Linkedin
linkedin.com/in/murad-nərimanlı-549389130

Github

murad-narimanli.github.io/

# Languages

Azerbaijani

**English** 

Russian

# Skills

- HTML5 CSS 3 Sass Scss
- Bootstrap
- Ant design
- Javascript (ES6, ITFES, OOP, Closures)
- Jquery (AAX, DOM, Objects, Arrays)
- Next. js
- ReactJS, VueJS, AngularJS
- Redux/Redux Toolkit
- Hooks
- UI Frameworks (Material Design)
- Vuex
- Nuxt
- NodeJS, ExpressJS
- RxJs, Grunt, Lodash, Underscore, D3
- Thunk
- Axios
- Rest Api

# **MURAD NARIMANLI**

I am a solution-oriented Senior Front End Developer skilled in contributing to a highly collaborative work environment with over 6 years of proven experience Able to effectively manage independent projects and collaborate as part of a productive team with consistent communication, leadership and technical background.

# **Senior Front End Developer**

# **Education**

Azerbaijan State Oil and Industry University Programming and automation | Master

Azerbaijan State Oil and Industry University Telecommunication engineering | Bachelor

# **Experience**

Aug 2021 - Present

# "Rabitabank" OJSC

# Lead Frontend developer

- -Technical support for Internet Banking system.
- -Writing new features
- -Bug fixing in the system.

Reference Head of development

+994515313311 - Aga SafaraLivev

Dec 2022 - Sep 2023.

# Fourmeta agency Frontend developer (remote)

- -Writing new features
- -Bug fixing in the system.

Reference CTO Artur Mihno

artur.mihno@fourmeta.com

Sept 2022 - January 2023.

#### Webzool Creative Company

Frontend developer (remote)

- Technichal support for online casino systems

Reference Team Lead

+994559991770 - Nizami Suleymanov

Aug 2022 - Sep 2023.

#### **Social Innovation Lab**

# Frontend instructor

- Teach a development skills to the new dev guys :D

Reference Course Director

+994556252621- Elnur Isazade

Aug 2019 - Aug 2023

#### **Timesoft**

### Frontend developer

- Writing internal control systems
- Solving technical problems in analyzing modules and submoduls

Reference Team Lead

+994558816768 - Abbas Makhsudov

June 2017 - Aug 2019

## "Okmedia" LLC

#### Frontend developer

- Making cooparative advertising and e-commerce websites
- Adapting the given design to the web

Reference CEO Eldar Ehmedzade

+994 55 585 75 35 eldar@okmedia.az

- Graphql
- NPM, npm bower yarn, Charts
- Gulp, Webpack
- Postman | Swagger
- Git Github Bitbucket
- C# & Python
- Asp .Netframework, .Net core MVC
- System Design
- MS SQL, MySQL, MongoDB
- Adobe Xd
- Fiqma
- Zeplin
- Sketch

# **Main Portfolio Projects**

# Internet Banking of "RabitaBank" OJSC

https://ib.rabitabank.com/

- Online credit order.
- Online Account Creation Service
- Online Salary Card order and Salary payment Projects
- Invoice Creation Service
- Anipay Payment system integration.

# CBM engineering internal system (private)

- Online certificate creation
- Creating certification skills for oil companies
- Approving oil quality for sale
- Registration system for this companies.
- Client side PDF export (Without backend)

#### **ITICKET.AZ**

# https://iticket.az/

- Online ticket sales platform
- 3D hall system with three js

#### Agros.az

#### https://agros.az/

- Agro management system
- Human resources module
- Garage module
- Online area management map
- Online car navigation and tracking system

#### Ledger Investing

https://www.ledgerinvesting.com/

#### **Bitplay**

https://bitplay.ag/

#### Cryptosino

https://cryptosino.cc/

#### Vac.az

https://vac.az/

### **Game Islands**

https://gamesislands.com/

#### RiverMonster

https://rivermonster-casino.com/

#### Vagasx

https://vegasx-casino.com/

## Flamingo7

https://flamingo7-casino.com/

## Ultrapower

https://ultrapower-casino.com/

# Evin.az

https://evin.az/

### Glitex.az

https://giltex.az/

# Lareine.az

https://lareine.az/

# Dosttech.az

https://dosttech.az/

# Ucuzagetdi.com

https://ucuzagetdi.com/

#### **Bravo Travel**

https://bravotravel.az/

#### Eurowin.az

https://eurowin.az/

#### Mirashotel.az

https://mirashotel.az/

# Khatailigt.az

https://khatailight.az/